Download Latest Movies & Seires From "WWW.MSMOVIESBD.COM"
For thousands of years, religious Jews
have praticed the ritual of "the vigil"-
When a member of the
community dies, the body is
watched round-the-clock
in shofts by a Shomer, or
watchamn, who recites the
Psalms to comfort the
deceased's soul and protect
it from unseen evil.
This watchman is typically a family member
or friend, but there are paid Shomers...
Hired to sit the vigil
when no one else can.
Stop acting crazy!
I wish that'd happen to me.
You know what I mean?
An old, fat Goy with terrible teeth?
- Drunk on the street.
Oh, great...
I want to talk to him for just a minute.
I only want to ask him something.
How are you?
You look a little exhausted...
- I'm good.
How are things going
with this new lifestyle?
Listen, I didn't...
I didn't want to push you away or anything.
I'm not trying to pry or get
into your business either.
It's just that I think about you
all the time. You understand?
You said you had a question.
I need you to be a Shomer. Tonight.
I will pay you.
I know you could use the money.
And I know you have trouble with rent...
- How do you know that?
How do you know that?
Why's it matter? I'll give
you $200 dollars, cash.
Right now.
For how long?
Five hours.
From now until the morning.
We had someone.
But he changed his mind and left suddenly.
$300.
You came to me?
Right?
Yeah.
You're desperate, right? You need me.
Right?
Ok. So $500.
I used to do this all the time.
I'll give you $400. Not a dollar more.
I knew right away you'd take this job.
And I know you're doing it for the money
but it's nothing to be ashamed of.
I honestly wanted to ask
you because sitting the
vigil, it brings you
closer to the community.
Wow. This is...
It is truly God's plan.
It's just that when you sit the vigil,
it's holy. It brings you back to us.
You've been feeling down.
We can talk things
through. Maybe tonight
will even help a bit...
So Shulem, who is the deceased?
He's Rubin Litvak, did you know him?
- No.
He was a good man, a little weird.
He was a Holocaust survivor
who made it through
the war but lost his
entire family there.
After the war, he started a family here...
But then he became a recluse,
estranged from his kids and grandchildren.
He hadn't left his home in years.
It's a really sad story.
He used to say that
whenever he stepped out of
his house, it was like he
was in absolute agony.
The other Shomer just ran out.
I trusted him, he's
family, but he left the job
because he was afraid...
Afraid?
That's what he said.
Why was he afraid?
Mr. Litvak's wife suffers from
Alzheimer's and is quite frail.
She'll likely sleep through the night.
It'll be quiet.
Here we are.
He will be the Shomer tonight.
He's an experienced Shomer. He sat the
vigil for Moshe Kellner, Chaim Sturman...
I know that you had a very
difficult and upsetting day.
But this will be good, it'll be good...
She'll sleep, don't worry about it.
The mortuary guys will be here at dawn.
The mortuary men will be here in...
...five hours.
If you have any problems, my house...
I'm saying that if there is
a problem, I'm close by.
It'd be nice if you'd join
us for the morning prayers.
Look I'm not trying to push you.
All I'm saying is
that it might be difficult
being here all night and...
...if you want to chat about
it later, come to synagogue.
Okay. No problem. I hope
everything goes well.
See ya later.
How to talk to women
- Top 10 Ways to Start Talking to Women
- 8 Successful Ways to Talk to Women
- How to have an actual
conversation with a woman
- Step-by-Step: How to Talk to Women
- The Art of Talking to Women
Is anyone here?
Mazzik July 271979
You told me Lieb could do magic.
He couldn't do anything!
- I never said he could really do magic!
Yes, you did!
I'll show you someday.
Promise?
God willing.
Sarah Hi
Hey.
New message from Sarah
Sarah What're you doing?
Working. I'm Shomer for the night.
I should not be on my phone.
Sarah
Ok. Sorry :(
No. It's ok.
What are you...
Sarah It's a pretty night.
The moon is out.
You ever see the rabbit in it?
Rabbit?
Sarah The nose is facing up,
little tail at the bottom.
It's silly.
I should let you go.
Not silly.
Talk soon.
Sarah
Call me or FaceTime if you get bored ;)
New Message From Uknown Number
media file not found
Pull yourself together.
I'm losing my mind.
I'm going crazy.
I let them hurt you...
I couldn't...
I couldn't move.
I let them hurt you...
Of course.
INCOMING FACETIME Sarah
You need to go upstairs, Yacov.
There is no point in fighting.
You watched Burech scream.
Watched him cry for you.
And you didn't move.
You just let him die.
I know.
I was scared...
Please forgive me.
I was...
I was scared.
Are you ok?
So did you have a good night?
Any problems? Anything come up?
Sure?
Of course.
Well, let me give you what I promised you.
Mrs. Litvak?
As I mentioned yesterday,
I truly hoped this
experience might give you a
new perspective on life.
I hoped we could talk about it.
Come with me to morning prayers.
Will you come with me to morning prayers?
I know you mean well.
I know this.
Sarah
Ugh, I'm up early. How was your night?
Coffee?
Don't Forget To Visit Our Movie Website "WWW.MSMOVIESBD.COM"